PATRICIA CARR

PERSONAL WEBSITE: https://pcarrhi.github.io

ABOUT

My experience in managing all the Communications of a growing company allowed me to understand the importance of KPIs and its influence on decision making.

I transitioned into the Web
Development field to challenge
myself on learning new languages
and gain new technical skills.
An enriching experience at Altran
helped me get a first experience
working with the Dev team for Best
Practices that contributes to a
project's success.

EDUCATION

Coding Academy by EPITECH

(European Institute of Technology) Certificate of Completion Oct 2019-July 2020

University of Hawaii at Manoa

BA Communications & French, 2013 French Honor Society, Lambda Pi Eta

CONTACT

- +33 (0)6 51 82 03 56
- pcarr.hi@gmail.com
- Toulouse, France

SKILLS

Marketing/Tools:

- Google Analytics
- Copywriting
- PR / Presentations
- MS Office
- Agile Framework (JIRA and Confluence)

Programming experience:

- Angular 8/9
- HTML5/CSS3/Styled
- React
- Components
- Python
- Firebase
- Mongo, Express, Node, React

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

ALTRAN (PART OF CAPGEMINI)

MARCH 2020- JULY 2020 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Work with project managers and other developers to understand each feature and time of completion to build components
- Review and utilize existing codebase to correct Front-End bug problems with team using Angular 8 and React
- Communicate with teammates on daily basis regarding code or technical issues

COMMUNICATIONS MANAGER

UWINLOC

JUN 2016- MAY 2019 - TOULOUSE, FRANCE

- Generate leads via videos, blogs, posters, website content.
- Maintain Press relations with journalists & Press Releases
- Internal Communication
- Manage social media content as well as KPI tracking
- Website Management through Wordpress
- Conduct Business Presentations/Pitching for new partnerships in France and within EU, USA, Japan, China
- Organize event logistics to maximize visibility at trade shows

PROJECT COORDINATOR

ALLIANCE FOUNDATION TRIALS

JULY 2014 - OCT 2015 - BOSTON, USA

- Document management for clinical online portal
- Event Logistics Support Biannual Pharma trade show
- · Meeting Minutes for Executive Board
- · Feasibility study tracking for CRMs